

1800 102 2558 | +91 9818882211







Assistant Manager seeking roles in Project Management, Strategy
Development, Production Engineering, Production Support, Design &
Development, Process Engineering, Root Cause Analysis, Client Management, Resource
Optimization, Cost Control, COBOL



Total Experience: 12 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Highest Degree: MS/MSc(Science) [master of science

Notice Period: 1 Month

in information Technology

Current Designation: Assistant Manager - Project

Management

Current Company: Renault Nissan Technology & Business

Centre India Pvt. Ltd

Current Location: Chennai

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Maintenance

Role: Project Lead

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Project Management, Strategy Development, Production Engineering, Production Support, Design & Development, Process Engineering, Root Cause Analysis, Client Management, Resource Optimization, Cost

Control, COBOL

Verified : Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 23-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Persuasive & influential leader, offering over 12 years of rich & extensive experience which includes 6 years in production support, Analysis, Design, Development and 6+ years of relevant work experience in Mainframe Technology

Managed full life cycle of applications in Manufacturing (Supply Chain Management)

Experienced in agile method project, and worked on agile methodology (Scrum)

Evaluated reporting to identify redundancies, automated solutions, and efficiencies to minimize manual processes

Delivered strategic consulting services to assist clients in all aspects of establishing an effective Big Data program, including people (roles and organization), processes, and technologies to meet client requirements

Collaborated with process engineering and product development teams for seamless transition of new products into production

Work Experience

Renault Nissan Technology & Business Centre India Pvt. Ltd as Assistant Manager - Project Management

Sep 2008 to Till Date

Growth Path:

Sr. Engineer 2008-2013 Assistant Manager 2013-2020

Project Executed

Project 1: Project Guarantee and Contract Service (PGCS) & Distribution System

Client: Renault (In-House) Role: Team Member Team Size: 20

Period: Feb'13-Apr'18/ May19-Present

Description:

Renault is a French multinational automobile manufacturer. Dealers and People working in the Warranty Platform are the users of PGCS System. Customer of Renault brings his vehicle to Dealer for reparation. Dealer decides whether to do reparation or not Dealer through the DMS or GCM1 applications sends the invoice to Renault. The Invoices received by Renault and processed daily in a night batch. If the Invoice is validated, it goes to further processing of payment else goes back to Dealer for correction. All the validated claims are processed for payment monthly and the information is sent to external systems for doing payment to Dealer. Contract details are set in CTA, country, language, dealer setup is done in RFR, special technical support for Recall operations done by OTS and GRM

1

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld. Key Result Areas:

Facilitated sprint plan and coordinated for project schedules, goals and milestones

Worked closely with product owners and business

Analyzed the requirement, design and development of the enhancement and change requests

Managed any production/acceptance defects

Formulated performance analysis an validated output

Contributed in agile meetings for continuous process

Provided right clarifications to the team and implemented team building & project management activities

Training and mentoring the fresher's in the team and ensured team follows right process

Project 2: Data Platform Support

Client: Renault (In-House)

Role: Team Member

Team Size: 6

Technology. Hortonworks Data Platform (HDP), Hortonworks Data Flow(HDF)

Period: May18-Apr'19

Key Result Areas:

Managed the Datalake platform, Nlfi workflows and supported Hive, HDFS

Coordinated with stakeholders and provided guidance and recommendation to familiarize with

Hadoop components

Understood Hadoop and Eco system Log Files

Formulated performance tuning of YARN, Hive, for better Hadoop environment experience and

performance

Monitored the jobs in Oozie for failure logs and analysis in Yarn

Supervised the components availability Hue, Edge Machine, Grafana, Ambari, Yarn, Spotfire

connectivity, DBeaver with Hive

Verified Kafka in Ambari, NiFi Node verification for 5 Node cluster, 2 Nodes Cluster & Single Node

cluster

Corroborated ingestions process source to transit flags status check for database

Project 3: RPL Migration to COBOL (Testing)

Client: Renault (In-House)

Role: Team Member Team Size: 23

Period: Sep'08-Jan'13

Description:

Renault uses the RPL (Renault programming language) is an 'in-house' development language to support all the Renault business applications. The main objective of the project is to convert RPL language components to COBOL language components. The scope of this project is huge, converting 33 million lines of code over a period of 5 years. The approach for conversion is based on ISO functionality, which includes a bug in RPL, will still be a bug in COBOL. Developed a translator engine that will read line by line of RPL code and convert into COBOL

Key Result Areas:

Mgrated code using the third-party tool

Debugged the issues to meet the actual requirements and validated the issues

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: BCA (Computers) from RNM College, Rajahmundry in 2002

PG: MS/M.Sc(Science) (master of science in information Technology) from Vels College of Science, Chennai in 2004

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
COBOL, PLI/1, JCL		
MVS,DB2 and IMS DB		
VSAM,CICS		
CHANGEMAN, FILEAID M/S, FILEAID DB2		
OPC, SAVERS, DRMS		
SNDMQA-Hiperstation, LDD+		
COPE, IMSConnect, LDD		
HP-Quality Center/Chipre, IDz, JIRA		

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Telugu				
Tamil				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No.

i ilyoloaliy Orlanoliyou. I to

оор турол оппанон

Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.